{
    "subject": "resource/Conrad_Letzkau",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Mayor of Danzig",
    "human_readable": "Conrad Letzkau is briefly described as 'Mayor of Danzig'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9368290305137634,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Danzig during Conrad Letzkau's time as mayor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8724014163017273,
            "question": "What challenges might a mayor of Danzig have faced during Conrad Letzkau's era?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8271669745445251,
            "question": "In what city did Conrad Letzkau serve as mayor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8271065950393677,
            "question": "What was Conrad Letzkau's role in Danzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7589700222015381,
            "question": "When did Conrad Letzkau likely serve as mayor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7002235651016235,
            "question": "Were there any notable events or policies associated with Conrad Letzkau's mayorship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.679519772529602,
            "question": "Who was Conrad Letzkau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5302109122276306,
            "question": "What is the significance of Conrad Letzkau's position?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4277573823928833,
            "question": "How is Conrad Letzkau remembered in history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3513791859149933,
            "question": "Are there any primary sources that provide insights into Conrad Letzkau's life and work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Conrad Letzkau is briefly described as 'Mayor of Danzig'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1238_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Conrad Letzkau remembered in history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1238_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of Conrad Letzkau's position?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1238_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Conrad Letzkau?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1238_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1238_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation result:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information about Conrad Letzkau being assassinated by the Teutonic Knights and his role as a mayor are mentioned in one of the documents. Therefore, it supports the statement that he is briefly described as \"Mayor of Danzig.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}